Where am I?
Am I dreaming?
Think of it as
being transported
to a cultivation world.
This world's supreme ruler, Shenlyu...
The Yellow Dragon made a prophecy:
only you can save the Xuanji Realm.
(A mortal body, a heaven-burning fate)
Your destiny lies here.
If you let me cultivate with you,
I'll fight for you.
Kill him!
(From Kuaikan Comic's "The Great Queen")
Don't you touch her!
(By Ao Xiaoze)
My life
isn't yours to take.
=The Great Queen=
(Adapted from Kuaikan Comic's exclusive
series "The Great Queen" by Ao Xiaoze)
=Episode 1=
(Huyun Kingdom)
(The Crown Prince's bedchamber really is
hard to sneak into.)
(Huyun Tribute Maiden Chi Yuan)
(Huyun's consort selection nears.)
(So many fierce rivals.)
(Tonight,
I just need to get to him first.)
(Huyun Crown Prince Jin Yunlie)
(Once I sleep with the Crown Prince,)
(I'll become Crown Princess)
(without lifting a finger.)
Your Highness,
allow me
to serve you tonight.
Shall I?
What's going on?
What's happened to me?
Mom,
(Modern girl Xi Yuan)
I got the job!
Ugh, you're so annoying!
You walking disaster!
What's the fricking yelling for?
Get the hell out of here!
Your Highness, are you injured?
I'm fine.
The assassin got away.
After them.
Right away.
Your Highness,
who is she?
I was about to ask you,
Lou Jingou.
How did a woman get into my bedchamber?
Let me check.
She seems to be
a tribute maiden from Jinghua Palace.
Her name is
Xi Yuan.
Xi Yuan?
I think I've seen this maiden before.
She always sneaks around watching you.
She must be a devoted admirer of yours.
Summon the Spirit Healer.
Understood.
(A devoted admirer?)
(Is it that simple?)
(Am I going to die?)
(He can save you.)
Who's there?
Who's talking?
Who are you?
(Xuanji Realm Supreme Ruler: Shisi)
♪I shut out the world, you're all I see♪
♪One glance to last forever,
just you and me♪
What's going on?
I'm completely healed?
How did you recover so fast?
(Huh? Where'd he go?)
What sorcery is this?
Your Highness,
the Spirit Healer is here.
Huh?
Your Highness, what...
(Everything about this woman seems off.)
Your Highness,
forget the maiden for now.
The Demon Lord's seal is weakening.
His Majesty summons you at once.
Father.
(Huyun King: Jin Yunling)
The seal is weakening.
You must hurry.
Whoa!
Where is this?
Am I dreaming?
What the hell?
It's you?
Did you bring me here?
And what happened just now
was your doing too?
Who are you exactly?
Your destiny lies here,
so you can't leave.
The moment you even think of leaving,
you'll suffer the agony of
your soul being torn away.
(What's happening?)
(Fine, whatever.)
(Even if I go back, I'll...)
I... I won't leave.
The pain's gone.
Think of it as
being transported
to a cultivation world.
This world's supreme ruler, Shenlyu,
is a cruel tyrant.
He used the Xuanji Jade
to spark war among the four kingdoms:
Huangyan, Longyuan, Xuanhan, and Huyun.
You must overthrow Shenlyu's rule
and save the Xuanji Realm.
You have to succeed.
Failure is not an option.
Your first mission is
to win the Huyun Crown Princess
Martial Trial.
Wait!
I don't know...
I know you're clueless.
So,
as your guide in this world,
I'll offer a bit of help.
I don't...
Disobey, and you die.
Then pick someone else...
No. It has to be you.
But if I...
If you fail the mission, you die too.
Fine.
So tell me,
what do I do right now?
A phone?
Isn't this a cultivation world?
Why is there a phone?
What is this?
Battle mode?
The Huyun tribute maiden selection
is decided by Spiritual Power.
You've just arrived in Xuanji Realm.
You need someone
to unlock your Spirit Core
before you can cultivate.
Spirit Core?
Is it like unlocking my meridians?
Something like that.
And...
Huh?
Where'd you go?
You haven't told me how to use it!
So you're Xi Yuan.
(Xia Honglian, 19,
daughter of Chancellor Xia Ling)
(Fiery temper, openly obsessed with
Crown Prince Jin Yunlie)
(Spiritual Element: Fire)
Xia Honglian?
Why did you hit me?
You can't even handle this much?
Seems you need more training.
Yes,
Father.
If you hadn't crawled
into his bed last night
and stolen my glory,
I would've been the one
who saved the Crown Prince.
I worked so hard to set up
that whole scheme,
and you just swooped in
and reaped the rewards.
Today,
you'll pay with your life!
A thousand years ago,
the Huyun Deity defeated him
and sealed him beneath our palace.
However,
human greed, desire,
and obsession never end,
so the Demon Lord can never
be truly destroyed.
If not for your half-human,
half-demon body,
which can absorb Demonic Energy
and serve as the seal,
the world would've become
a living hell long ago.
Yunlie,
you are Huyun's hero.
You give me too much credit, Father.
As the Crown Prince of Huyun,
I must do all I can.
Absorbing the Demonic Energy
drains your spirit.
Go back and rest now.
I take my leave.
(Too slow.)
(Still too slow.)
Let go!
Let me go!
My lady, don't do it!
She saved His Highness.
If she dies here,
you could be held responsible.
Since you love crawling into
men's beds so much,
then
I'll make sure you get your fill.
What are you doing?
(This drug is called Spring Dream.)
(The only way to neutralize it)
(is to sleep with someone.)
(I've already prepared it just for you.)
Help me.
Please, help me.
(Xi Yuan's Sea of Consciousness)
You...
Your Spirit Core hasn't been unlocked?
I feel so hot...
I'm burning up...
Help me...
♪A love letter, a passionate pursuit,
the envy of everyone♪
♪Bouquets and heartfelt confessions,
leaving me moved and fulfilled♪
♪No matter how long or hard our road,
I don't care♪
♪But you left me with this pain,
forever beyond redemption♪